

# **NGUYEN VAN A**

# **MARKETING MANAGER**

Male

**May 19, 1992** 

♥ Hanoi, Vietnam

fb.com/quynhtom design

Take advantages of sales skills & experience and sum, và đã nghiên cứu tất cả các ứng dụng của từ này trong văn học cổ điển, đ of market to become a professional Sales Staff and bring a lot value to Customers. From that, I will contribute to development of CVPRO Company.

## **EDUCATION**



## **FOREIGN TRADE UNIVERSITY**

major. abo. Nemo administration

m Sep 2007 - Present

#### **FOREIGN TRADE UNIVERSITY**

major. corporate administration

mm Sep 2007 - Present

## **EXPERIENCE**



Sep 2007 - Present

#### **CVPRO JSC**

Sale Executive

# Main responsibilities:

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult, vel illum qui do and answer customers' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to control goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

#### **Recognition and Gains:**

- Advertising products of the Company to customers effectively: contribute to a 20% increase in the number of customers within one month of working

Sep 2007 - Present

#### **CVPRO JSC**

Sale Executive

## Main responsibilities:

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult products and answer customers' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to who fail in their duty through weakness of will, which is the sa goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

Recognition and Gains:

- Advertising products of the Company to customers effectively: contribute to a 20% increase in the number of customers within one month of working





## **CVPRO JSC**

#### Sale Executive

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult products and answer nderit in voluptate velit esse cillum dolore eu fugiat nulla pariatur. Excepteur sin' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to control goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

# **CERTIFICATIONS**



**TOEIC Certificate With Score 800 Issued By CVPRO** 2004

# **HONORS & AWARDS**



**TOEIC Certificate With Score 800 Issued By CVPRO** 

2013 - 2014

# **ADDITIONAL INFORMATION**



- Organize monthly events, network with US alumni
- Share how to hunt scholarships and US student's life experiences to all students who have received offers from US ident, somet

#### **REFERENCES**



## **NGUYEN VAN BINH**

director of cvpro jsc

mbinhnv@topcv.com **U** 01234567890

## **SKILLS**



Words Photoshop Excel English Power Point • Japanese

# **INTERESTS**



- Organize monthly events, network with US alumni
- Share how to hunt and US student's life experiences to all students who have received offers from US universities